Guide to the Clara Fraser Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Clara Fraser papers, 1923-1998; 3187-003; 20.61 cubic feet 22 boxes
  - Clara Fraser vs. Seattle City Light Employment Discrimination Case Records, Series 12
    - Transcript Excerpts, 1980
      - 22-SPa GV believed influenced ETT selection, 1980 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - 22-SPc ETTs sincerely motivated to be electrical workers, 1980 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - 22-SPd Management believed CF manipulated ETTs protest, 1980 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - 22-SPe ETTs self-motivated in complaints, 1980 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - 25-SP BR informed and satisfied with ETT plan, 1980 (Box-folder 10/15)
      - 29-SP ETT cancellation not discussed, 1980 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - 34-SP CF too much an advocate for women's rights, 1980 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - 36-SP GV couldn't separate politics from performance, 1980 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - 37-SP GV and management discussed CF as radical during walkout, 1980 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - 37-SP Some management wanted CF fired for PRC testimony, 1980 (Box-folder 10/20)
      - 38-SP GV and management knew of CF's P-I and conduct, 1980 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - 63-SP GV - political and called CF radical, 1980 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - 65-SP "Karl Marx" quote, 1980 (Box-folder 10/23)
      - 66-SP Management disparagement of CF's politics, 1980 (Box-folder 10/24)
      - 67-SP CF's activities affected lay-off determination, 1980 (Box-folder 10/25)
      - 79-SP Cf's conduct tied to beliefs, 1980 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - 85-SP No action against BR for poor job, 1980 (Box-folder 10/27)
      - 6-A/S Goldsmith - why brought in, 1980 (Box-folder 10/28)
      - 14-A/Sa Problems in training, etc. were Cf's fault (general incompetence), 1980 (Box-folder 10/29)
      - 14-A/Sb CF poor performance interface with management, 1980 (Box-folder 10/30)
      - 14-A/Se Performance - plunge in without management approval, 1980 (Box-folder 10/31)
      - 14-A/Se Perfomance - shorthand $50,000 cost and low priority, 1980 (Box-folder 10/32)
      - 22-A/S CF non-disclosure of ETT relationships was disruptive, 1980 (Box-folder 10/33)
      - 71-A/S Wolak more qualified than CF, 1980 (Box-folder 10/34)
      - Pleadings, filings and decisions before Superior Court, case 80-2-12077-8, 1980-1983
      - Complaint for declaratory judgment, 1980 (Box-folder 10/35)
      - Writ of certiorari, 1980 (Box-folder 10/36)
      - Jewett to Ponder 8/14/1980 (Box-folder 10/37)
      - City's motion to dismiss declaratory judgment 8/26/1980 (Box-folder 10/38)
      - Transcript of hearing before Judge Cushing re declaratory judgment 9/4/1980 (Box-folder 10/39)
      - Our motions, etc. for 9/18/1980 hearing (Box-folder 10/40)
      - Writ of certiorari 9/11/1980 (Box-folder 10/41)
      - Order of dismissal, 1980 (Box-folder 10/42)
      - Order of certiorari and allocation of transcription costs, 1980 (Box-folder 10/43)
      - Affidavit of Elizabeth Ponder 9/21/1980 (Box-folder 10/44)
      - Affidavit of Fred Hyde 9/22/1980 (Box-folder 10/45)
      - Supplementary memos answering City Attorney 9/23/1980 (Box-folder 10/46)
      - Brief 9/23/1980 (Box-folder 10/47)
      - Clara's notes on 9/23/1980 hearing (Box-folder 10/48)
      - Transcript of Corbett's decision 9/23/1980 (Box-folder 10/49)
      - Notice of presentation of order off dismissal 9/24/1980 (Box-folder 10/50)
      - Filings and decisions October, 1980 (Box-folder 10/51)
      - Indigency order 11/15/1980 (Box-folder 10/52)
      - Filings and decisions December, 1980 (Box-folder 10/53)
      - Filings and decisions January, 1981 (Box-folder 10/54)
      - Filings and decisions February, 1981 (Box-folder 10/55)
      - Response to motion for discretionary review (draft), 1981 (Box-folder 10/56)
      - Commissioner's ruling denying petition for discretionary review, 1981 (Box-folder 10/57)
      - Response to motion for discretionary review, 1981 (Box-folder 10/58)
      - Objections to transcripts 7/18/1981 (Box-folder 10/59)
      - Respondent's corrections to transcripts 7/20/1981 (Box-folder 10/60)
      - Motion for settlement of bill of exceptions 7/25/1981 (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Petitioner's response to city's corrections to transcript 7/25/1981 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Motion to include documents 7/27/1981 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - City response to objections to transcript 7/27/1981 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - City motions on exceptions and response, 1981 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Indexes to exhibits and documents, 1981 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - Filings and decisions August 1981 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Filings and decisions September 1981 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Filings and decisions October 1981 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - Filings and decisions November 1981 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Transcript of hearing before Judge Corbett 12/30/1981 (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Filings and decisions December 1981 (part 1 of 2) (Box-folder 11/12)
      - Filings and decisions December 1981 (part 2 of 2) (Box-folder 11/13)
      - Filings and decisions January, 1982 (Box-folder 11/14)
      - Filings and decisions February, 1982 (Box-folder 11/15)
      - Opening appeal brief 3/15/1982 (Box-folder 11/16)
      - City stipulation/order modifying brief schedule 5/16/1982 (Box-folder 11/17)
      - Brief materials 5/18/1982 (Box-folder 11/18)
      - Fraser reply brief 5/19/1982 (Box-folder 11/19)
      - City's brief in answer to Fraser 6/1/1982 (Box-folder 11/20)
      - Memos of conversation June 1982 (Box-folder 11/21)
      - Val's notes from discussion with Barb Stendahl 7/23/1982 (Box-folder 11/22)
      - Fraser's motion for inclusion of additional evidence 8/3/1982 (Box-folder 11/23)
      - City's motion for summary judgment - Beckwith fees, 1982 (Box-folder 11/24)
      - Appeal trial visual aids, 1982 (Box-folder 11/25)
      - Transcript of decision, 1982 (Box-folder 11/26)
      - City's motion for reconsideration, 1982 (Box-folder 11/27)
      - Notice and presentation of findings of fact and conclusions, 1982 (Box-folder 11/28)
      - Application for attorney's fees - Beckwith, 1982 (Box-folder 11/29)
      - City's objections to findings of fact and conclusions, 1982 (Box-folder 11/30)
      - Order reinstating Hearing Examiner decision, 1982 (Box-folder 11/31)
      - Filings and correspondence on back pay and expenses, 1982 (Box-folder 11/32)
      - Abstract of Superior Court judgment, 1982 (Box-folder 11/33)
      - Freds/Vals affidavits re fees, 1982 (Box-folder 11/34)
      - Beckwith appeal, 1982 (Box-folder 11/35)
      - Attorney's fees, 1983 (Box-folder 11/36)
      - Beckwith appeal, 1983 (Box-folder 11/37)
      - Transcript of Goodloe's decision re attorney's fees, 1983 (Box-folder 11/38)
      - Index to legal documents, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 11/39)
    - Case Administration Files, 1977-1985
      - Legal correspondence, 1980 (Box-folder 11/40)
      - Legal correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1981 (Box-folder 11/41)
      - Legal correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1981 (Box-folder 11/42)
      - Legal correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 11/43)
      - Summary of updated damages, 1982 (Box-folder 11/44)
      - Stipulation on damages, 1982 (Box-folder 11/45)
      - Damages, 1980 (Box-folder 11/46)
      - Damages update to 9/82, 1982 (Box-folder 11/47)
      - Damages to 1980 (Box-folder 11/48)
      - Background on Goodloe, 1982 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Hearing panel, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Commission rules for panelist, 1977 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Human Rights Department consolidation, 1980 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Darlen Allison, 1980 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Notes on meetings, 1980 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Transcript preparation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Office for Women's Rights, 1980 (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Salmi to Board of Ethics 9/15/80, 1980 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Hyde statement on rules governing employment discrimination and open housing proceedings, 1980 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - City Light reorganization, 1980 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Memos to City Light employees, 1980 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - General correspondence, 1980 (Box-folder 12/13)
      - General correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - General correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - General correspondence, 1983; Photographs: includes 4 35mm b&w negatives (Box-folder 12/16)
      - General correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 12/17)
      - Case administration, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - American Civil Liberties Union correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Clara Fraser vs. City Light congratulations / support, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 12/20)
      - John Chen Beckwith, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/21)
      - Mary Ann Curtis trip, 1982 (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Monica Hill, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12/23)
      - Sara Marsh, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Letter campaigns, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 12/25)
      - Related issues, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 12/26)
      - Obscene mail, 1980 (Box-folder 12/27)
      - Fundraising events, 1980 (Box-folder 12/28)
      - New Year's fundraiser, 1980 (Box-folder 12/29)
      - Aberdeen forum, 1981 (Box-folder 12/30)
      - Monica's going-away party, 1981 (Box-folder 12/31)
      - San Francisco Mime Troupe, 1981 (Box-folder 12/32)
      - Pangborn picnic, 1981 (Box-folder 12/33)
      - Joanna Russ event, 1981 (Box-folder 12/34)
      - Images of Labor benefit, 1981 (Box-folder 12/35)
      - New Year's Eve party, 1981 (Box-folder 12/36)
      - Clara Fraser visit to New York City, 1981 (Box-folder 12/37)
      - San Francisco victory party, 1982 (Box-folder 12/38)
      - National Lawyer Guild seminar, 1983 (Box-folder 12/39)
      - First anniversary celebration, 1983 (Box-folder 12/40)
      - Donations in-kind, 1981 (Box-folder 12/41)
      - Financial reports, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 12/42)
      - Fundraising, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/43)
      - Legal expenses, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 12/44)
      - Clara's personal finances, 1980 (Box-folder 12/45)
    - Related Cases, 1980-1985
      - Rod Handley vs. City Light, 1981 (Box-folder 12/46)
      - Lakshas case, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 12/47)
      - New York sex discrimination case and other related cases, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 12/48)
      - Other related cases, 1984 (Box-folder 12/49)
      - Merle Woo case: correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 12/50)
      - Merle Woo case: legal, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 12/51)
      - Merle Woo case: publicity (part 1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 12/52)
      - Merle Woo case: publicity (part 2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Merle Woo case: administration, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Post-Victory Projects, 1983-1984
      - Film, 1983 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Working women's conference: planning, 1984 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Working women's conference: report to Common Wealth Fund, 1984 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Working women's conference: conference packet, 1984 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Working women's conference: publicity, 1984 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Case Publicity, 1974-1987
      - Clara commendations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Case publicity, 1980 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Case publicity, 1908-1983 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - The Story of Clara Fraser vs. Seattle City Light, 1981 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - Resolutions on Clara's case, 1980 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Support organizing, 1983 (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Freeway Hall case, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Chronological Case Support Files, 1973-1988
      - Chronologies, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - Document lists, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - Correspondence and documents, 1973 (Box-folder 13/17)
      - City Light training job descriptions, 1973 (Box-folder 13/18)
      - Human relations training, 1973 (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Shorthand class, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13/20)
      - Public Review Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 13/21)
      - Correspondence and documents (part 1 of 4), 1974 (Box-folder 13/22)
      - Correspondence and documents (part 2 of 4), 1974 (Box-folder 13/23)
      - Correspondence and documents (part 3 of 4), 1974 (Box-folder 13/24)
      - Correspondence and documents (part 4 of 4), 1974 (Box-folder 13/25)
      - City Light press clippings May-September, 1974 (Box-folder 13/26)
      - Special women's programs, 1975 (Box-folder 13/27)
      - "Safety" poster protest letter, 1975 (Box-folder 13/28)
      - Bill of Rights and Responsibilities Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/29)
      - Layoff, 1975 (Box-folder 13/30)
      - Current events, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Unemployment insurance dispute, 1975 (Box-folder 13/32)
      - Correspondence and documents (part 1 of 3), 1975 (Box-folder 13/33)
      - Correspondence and documents (part 2 of 3), 1975 (Box-folder 13/34)
      - Correspondence and documents (part 3 of 3), 1975 (Box-folder 13/35)
      - Settlement of Electrical trades trainee case, 1976 (Box-folder 13/36)
      - Correspondence and documents, 1976 (Box-folder 13/37)
      - Durham, Back, Cornish documentation of harrassment on the job, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13/38)
      - Press releases and clippings, 1977 (Box-folder 13/39)
      - Teri Bach conversation with Mayor Royer about Clara Fraser case, 1979 (Box-folder 13/40)
      - Training Coordinator Civil Service exam protest and answer, 1976 (Box-folder 13/41)
      - City Light issues, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 13/42)
    - Supplemental Chronological Case Support Files, 1972-1976
      - Superintendent's staff meetings -- inadequate affirmative action programs, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Superintendent's staff meetings -- electrical trades trainee program background, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Correspondence and documents, 1973 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Correspondence and documents, 1974 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Correspondence and documents, 1975 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Electrical trades trainee case -- objections by Office of Women's Rights to Hearing Examiner's proposed findings and conclusions, 1976 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Electrical trades trainee case -- post-hearing brief of Office of Women's Rights, 1976 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Electrical trades trainee case -- exhibits admitted (part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Electrical trades trainee case -- exhibits admitted (part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - Electrical trades trainee case -- Megan Cornish's notes on hearing (part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Electrical trades trainee case -- Megan Cornish's notes on hearing (part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - City Light Background Files, 1980-1995; Series 13
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1983 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light rally, 1983 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1984 (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1985 (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1986 (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1987 (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1988 (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1989 (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1990 (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1991 (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1992 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light -- Human Rights Department case, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1993 (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1994 (Box-folder 14/25)
    - Committee for Equal Rights at City Light, 1995 (Box-folder 14/26)
    - City Light Work Environment Task Force, 1983 (Box-folder 14/27)
    - City Light, 1983 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - City Light organizing press coverage, 1983 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - City Light, 1984 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - City Light press coverage, 1984 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - City Light press coverage, 1985 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - City Light press coverage, 1986 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - City Light press coverage, 1987 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - City Light publicity and correspondence, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - City Light press coverage, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - City Light correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - City Light memos and press coverage, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Affirmative action, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Superintendent search, 1984 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Randy Hardy at City Light, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Superintendent Roberta Palm Bradley, 1994 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Human relations training, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - City Light co-workers, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 15/17)
    - Freedom Socialist Party City Light fraction work, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Teri Bach, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 15/19)
    - Heidi Durham post-ETT, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 15/20)
    - Letha Neal, 1983 (Box-folder 15/21)
    - City Light apprenticeship program, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 15/22)
    - City Light organization chart, 1982 (Box-folder 15/23)
    - Network (newsletter), 1991-1993 (Box-folder 15/24)
    - City of Seattle memos and press coverage, 1982-1993 (Box-folder 15/25)
    - Clara's City Light resume, etc., 1982 (Box-folder 15/26)
    - Clara's application for appointment to Human Rights Commission, 1986 (Box-folder 15/27)
    - City of Seattle -- City Attorney Doug Jewitt, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 15/28)
    - City of Seattle -- Mayor Norm Rice, 1990 (Box-folder 15/29)
  - Fraser Job Records while at City Light, 1971-1981; Series 14
    - Fire Department, 1971 (Box-folder 15/30)
    - Training projects, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 15/31)
    - Seattle City Light. Training catalog, 1974 (Box-folder 15/32)
    - Background materials on equal employment opportunities, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 15/33)
    - Training projects for women, 1973 (Box-folder 15/34)
    - Courses on women, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 15/35)
    - Interviewing - proper and improper, 1973 (Box-folder 15/36)
    - Seminars on women - announcements, 1974 (Box-folder 15/37)
    - History of women - presentation for Park Department, 1973 (Box-folder 15/38)
    - Instructor training course, 1973 (Box-folder 15/39)
    - You server the public course, 1973 (Box-folder 15/40)
    - Effective listening training, 1973 (Box-folder 15/41)
    - Management development seminar, 1973 (Box-folder 15/42)
    - Basic management functions course, 1973 (Box-folder 15/43)
    - Human relations workshop, 1973 (Box-folder 15/44)
    - Weekly memos to Bill Rheubottom, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 15/45)
    - Weekly memos to director, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Memos to Clara, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Memos from Vickery, etc, 1973 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Administrative tools - forms, charts, graphs, 1973 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Personnel handbook, 1973 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Memory development, 1973 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Labor relations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Seattle fair employment ordinance, 1973 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Johnny Walker case, 1974 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Sticky cases, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Women's strengthening exercizes, 1975 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - Discriminatory language, 1974 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - Press clippings on Gordon Vickery, 1979 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - Race and racism, 1973 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - City Light nuclear policy, 1976 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Uhlman editorial, 1976 (Box-folder 16/16)
    - City of Seattle affirmative action ordinance, 1972 (Box-folder 16/17)
    - General management, 1973 (Box-folder 16/18)
    - City of Seattle general, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16/19)
    - City Light phone lists, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 16/20)
    - City of Seattle background on affirmative action, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 16/21)
    - City Light history on affirmative action, 1972 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - Mayor Uhlman recall, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16/23)
    - Firefighters' Uhlman recall campaign, 1974 (Box-folder 16/24)
    - City Light walkout, 1974 (Box-folder 16/25)
    - Bill of Rights and Responsibilities -- final draft, 1975 (Box-folder 16/26)
    - Bill of Rights and Responsibilities -- rough drafts, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16/27)
    - Bill of Rights and Responsibilities Committee -- correspondence and press coverage, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16/28)
    - Public Review Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 16/29)
    - Clara's resume', 1973 (Box-folder 16/30)
    - Activity reports, 1973 (Box-folder 16/31)
    - Activity reports, 1974 (Box-folder 16/32)
    - Activity reports, 1975 (Box-folder 16/33)
    - Job task list, 1975 (Box-folder 16/34)
    - Memos from Clara, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 16/35)
    - Thank-yous to Clara, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 16/36)
    - Feminist Coordinating Council press release on Clara's "layoff", 1975 (Box-folder 16/37)
    - Press coverage of Clara's firing, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 16/38)
    - Clara Fraser correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 16/39)
    - Civil Service Board exam and Clara's firing, 1975 (Box-folder 16/40)
    - Daniggelis case, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16/41)
    - Daniggelis Defense Committee, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16/42)
    - Daniggelis case - Civil Service Commission, 1975 (Box-folder 16/43)
    - Daniggelis -- City Light rate hearings, 1974 (Box-folder 16/44)
    - Electrical Trades Trainee program (part 1 of 2), 1974 (Box-folder 16/45)
    - Electrical Trades Trainee program (part 2 of 2), 1974 (Box-folder 16/46)
    - Electrical Trades Trainee program, 1975 (Box-folder 16/47)
    - Trainee injunction hearing notes, 1975 (Box-folder 16/48)
    - June 8, 1974 hoax leaflet (Box-folder 16/49)
    - Electrical Trades Trainee case, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 16/50)
    - Apprenticeships, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 16/51)
    - Teri Bach apprenticeship, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 16/52)
    - Bach's expulsion from Small Strategy Committee, 1981 (Box-folder 16/53)
    - City Light strike, 1975 (Box-folder 16/54)
    - Local 77 organizing of office workers, 1974 (Box-folder 16/55)
    - Office workers organizing, 1974 (Box-folder 16/56)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers constitution, 1970 (Box-folder 16/57)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 - City Light, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 16/58)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 contracts, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 16/59)
    - City Light human relations training, 1973 (Box-folder 16/60)
    - City of Seattle and City Light training booklets, 1975 (Box-folder 16/61)
    - U. S. Department of Labor grant PC 1010, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 16/62)
  - Fraser job correspondence after return to City Light, 1982-1986; Series 15
    - City Light job, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Xeroxing project check list [serves as item-level index to correspondence], 1984 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Sick leave and vacation reports, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Notes, Undated (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Staff meetings, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1982 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Correspondence and reports January-February, 1983 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Correspondence and reports March-April, 1983 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Correspondence and reports May-June, 1983 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Correspondence and reports July-August, 1983 (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Correspondence and reports September-October, 1983 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Correspondence and reports November-December, 1983 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Correspondence and reports January-February, 1984 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Correspondence and reports March-April, 1984 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Correspondence and reports May, 1984 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Correspondence and reports June, 1984 (Box-folder 17/16)